Guide to the R. Stuart Hummel Family Papers M1607
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series VIII. GENEALOGY
  - Subseries II. RELATIVES OF WILLIAM F. HUMMEL
    - Caroline Wehking Hummel (Box 261, Folder 3)
    - Louis George Hummel (Box 261, Folder 4)
    - August Gottlieb Hummel (Box 261, Folder 5)
    - George August Hummel (Box 261, Folder 6)
    - George August Hummel (Box 261, Folder 7)
    - Walter Arthur Hummel (Box 261, Folder 8)
    - Evelyn Elizabeth Hummel (Box 261, Folder 9)
    - Marie Bernice Hummel (Box 262, Folder 1)
    - Marie Bernice Hummel (Box 262, Folder 2)
    - Homer Harold Hummel (Box 262, Folder 3)
    - Ervin Ralph Hummel (Box 262, Folder 4)
    - Paul William Hummel (Box 262, Folder 5)
    - Kenneth Louis Hummel (Box 262, Folder 6)
    - Phyllis Irene Hummel (Box 262, Folder 7)
    - Wesley Walter Hummel (Box 262, Folder 8)
    - Warren County, Missouri (Box 263, Folder 1)
    - Warren County, Missouri, Central Wesleyan College, 1914 (Box 263, Folder 2)
    - A History of the Pioneer Families of Missouri (photocopy), 1876 (Box 263, Folder 3)
    - Warren County, Missouri, Historical Society (Box 263, Folder 4)
    - Warren County, Missouri, Historical Society (Box 263, Folder 5)
    - Warren County, Missouri, miscellaneous maps and clippings (Flat-box 273, Folder 2)
    - Warren County, Missouri, historical atlases (Warren County Historical Society) (Flat-box 273, Folder 3)
    - Hummel family reunion, Warrengton-Truesdale, Missouri, 1990 (Box 263, Folder 6)
    - Hummel family reunion, Warrengton-Truesdale, Missouri, photographs, 1990 (Box 263, Folder 7)
    - Helen Ankersheil McCarty Hunter (Box 263, Folder 8)
    - Krughoff family: Henry L. and Ada (Box 264, Folder 1)
    - Krughoff family: Henry L. and Ada (Box 264, Folder 2)
    - Marie Louise Wehking Krughoff, 1864, October 25 - 1901, April 26 (Box 264, Folder 3)
    - Doris Ann Huelsman and Alfred F. Lang (Box 264, Folder 4)
    - Doris Ann Huelsman and Alfred F. Lang (Box 264, Folder 5)
    - Doris Ann Huelsman and Alfred F. Lang (Box 264, Folder 6)
    - Doris Ann Huelsman and Alfred F. Lang (Box 264, Folder 7)
    - Doris Ann Huelsman and Alfred F. Lang (Box 264, Folder 8)
    - Doris Ann Huelsman and Alfred F. Lang (Box 264, Folder 9)
    - "Solutions for Education" by Alfred F. Lang (Box 264, Folder 10)
    - "Virtues of Friendship" by Alfred F. Lang (Box 264, Folder 11)
    - Doris Ann Huelsman Lang (Box 265, Folder 1)
    - Doris Ann Huelsman Lang (Box 265, Folder 2)
    - Married to Food / Celebrating the Nuptials by Doris Ann Huelsman Lang (Box 265, Folder 3)
    - Aroused Russian Soul by Doris Ann Huelsman Lang (Box 265, Folder 4)
    - Lesemann family (Box 266, Folder 1)
    - Lesemann family (Box 266, Folder 2)
    - Ernst H. Lesemann diary, 1843-1875 (Box 266, Folder 3)
    - Geraldine B. Hummel Murphy (Box 266, Folder 4)
    - Geraldine B. Hummel Murphy (Box 266, Folder 5)
    - Geraldine B. Hummel Murphy (Box 266, Folder 6)
    - Rosina Charlotte Wehking Peitham, 1879, August 11 - 1966, May 17 (Box 266, Folder 7)
    - Rosina Charlotte Wehking Peitham, 1879, August 11 - 1966, May 17 (Box 266, Folder 8)
    - Rose Wehking Peitham copies/photo album (Box 266, Folder 9)
    - Margaret Wehking Perisho (Box 267, Folder 1)
    - Margaret Wehking Perisho (Box 267, Folder 2)
    - Wehking, Lessemann, etc., burial photos by R. J. Perisho (Box 267, Folder 3)
    - Martha Hummel and Charles Solter, letters, cards, photos from friends and relatives (Box 267, Folder 4)
    - Martha Hummel and Charles Solter, letters, cards, photos from friends and relatives (Box 267, Folder 5)
    - Martha Hummel and Charles Solter, letters, cards, photos from friends and relatives (Box 267, Folder 6)
    - Martha Hummel Solter (Box 267, Folder 7)
    - Martha Hummel Solter, items of "Inspiration and Strength" scrapbook (Box 267, Folder 8)
    - Martha Hummel Solter, death of Charles Solter and pre-paid funeral arrangements for Martha (Box 267, Folder 9)
    - Martha Hummel Solter, photocopies of "scrapbook" items (Box 267, Folder 10)
    - Martha Hummel Solter, miscellaneous (Box 267, Folder 11)
    - Martha Hummel Solter and Charles Solter, photographs, circa 1890 - 1908 (Box 268, Folder 1)
    - Martha Hummel Solter and Charles Solter, photographs, circa 1927 - 1950 (Box 268, Folder 2)
    - Martha Hummel Solter and Charles Solter, photgraphs, negatives, 1908 (Box 268, Folder 3)
    - Martha Hummel Solter and Charles Solter, photographs (Box 268, Folder 4)
    - Martha Hummel Solter and Charles Solter, photographs (Box 268, Folder 5)
    - Martha Hummel Solter and Charles Solter, photographs of friends and relatives (Box 268, Folder 6)
    - Strecker family line (Box 268, Folder 7)
    - Strecker family line (Box 268, Folder 8)
    - Strecker family line (Box 268, Folder 9)
    - Strecker family line (Box 268, Folder 10)
    - Strecker family documents (Box 268, Folder 11)
    - Johann David Strecker, 1794-1879 (Box 269, Folder 1)
    - George M. Strecker family (Box 269, Folder 2)
    - George M. Strecker family (Box 269, Folder 3)
    - Sophie Marie Elizabeth Wehking Wald, 1869 April 07 - 1955 August 12 (Box 269, Folder 4)
    - Wehking family line (Box 269, Folder 5)
    - Wehking family line (Box 269, Folder 6)
    - Wehking family line (Box 269, Folder 7)
    - Wehking family line (Box 269, Folder 8)
    - Wehking family line (Box 269, Folder 9)
    - Ernst Friedrich ludwig Louis Wehking, 1833 March 17 - 1903 November 24 (Box 270, Folder 1)
    - Ernst Friedrich Louis Wehking "Louis", 1872 September 4 - 1962 May 2 (Box 270, Folder 2)
    - Louise Christine Wehking Thee, 1866 December 13 - 1899 May 15 (Box 270, Folder 3)
    - Lydia Sophie Wehking Thee, 1876 October 18 - 1943 July 19 (Box 270, Folder 4)
    - Ella Josephine Wehking, 1882 August 12 - 1963 November 28 (Box 270, Folder 5)
    - Elmer Wehking, son of Louis Wehking Jr. (Box 270, Folder 6)
    - Waldo E. Wehking ("Sandy"), son of Louis Wehking Jr., circa 1960 to 1993 December 31 (Box 270, Folder 7)
  - Subseries III. MISCELLANEOUS GENEALOGY
    - Robert Knowles Hurd, "Monolith," typescript (Box 276, Folder 1)
    - Maurer family reunion, 1999 (Box 276, Folder 2)
    - R. Stuart Hummel, geneology charts (Box 260, Folder 2)
    - R. Stuart Hummel, notes for writing family history and diaries (Box 276, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous clippings (Box 276, Folder 4)
- Series IX. PHOTOGRAPHS, Circa 1870-2005
  The series contains the majority of the significant photographs in the collection. The photographs in this series document the Stuart family's early years in Wuhu, China (1886-1897), including the building of the Wuhu Methodist hospital; the Stuart and Hummel families' lives in Nanjing (1897-1927); students and faculty at the University of Nanking; Chinese friends and travels in China; Mildred Stuart Hummel's early life, college years, and travels; also included are photographs of R. Stuart and siblings as children in China as well as photographs of the 1927 Nanking Incident and its aftermath.
  Later materials in the series include R. Stuart's photographs from Honolulu, Hawaii, during World War II and photographs of his work and family life in Washington D.C.
  Photographs have been arranged in rough chronological order. Photographs in the collection are either loose in folders or in bound albums. Files labeled "Duplicates" may include duplicate copy prints or duplicate originals. Files labeled "Copy prints (unique)" contain copy prints for which it appeared that no original photograph was present in the collection. Some files also contain negatives and miscellaneous materials, such as notes and photocopied letters, found with the photographs.
  The majority of original photographs through 1950 are available online. Some photographs from late in this period (post 1930) have not been digitized due to third-party privacy concerns but selected post-1950 photographs such as the 1963 photograph of Mildred and William F. Hummel with the Chinese ambassador are available online.
  Materials in this series are available at the item level.
  - Stuart family, large portrait photographs, circa 1880s-1920s (Map-folder 281)
  - Stuart family, large portrait photographs, circa 1880s-1920s (Map-folder 282)
  - Rachel Anna Golden Stuart photographs, miscellaneous materials, circa 1870-1949 (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - Rachel Anna Golden Stuart photographs, circa 1870-1900 (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - Photo 1 (Box 104, Folder 2, Item 1)
    - Photo 2 (Box 104, Folder 2, Item 2)
    - Photo 3 (Box 104, Folder 2, Item 3)
    - Photo 4 (Box 104, Folder 2, Item 4)
    - Photo 5 (Box 104, Folder 2, Item 5)
    - Photo 6 (Box 104, Folder 2, Item 6)
    - Photo 7 (Box 104, Folder 2, Item 7)
    - Photo 8 (Box 104, Folder 2, Item 8)
    - Photo 9 (Box 104, Folder 2, Item 9)
    - Photo 10 (Box 104, Folder 2, Item 10)
    - Photo 11 (Box 104, Folder 2, Item 11)
    - Photo 12 (Box 104, Folder 2, Item 12)
  - Rachel Anna Golden Stuart photographs, circa 1930-1949 (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - Rachel Anna Golden Stuart photographs, copy prints (unique), circa 1870-1900 (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - Rachel Anna Golden Stuart photographs, copy prints (unique), circa 1900-1949 (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - Rachel Anna Golden Stuart photographs, duplicates, circa 1870-1949 (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - Rachel Anna Golden Stuart photographs, duplicates, circa 1870-1949 (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - Rachel Anna Golden Stuart photographs, negatives, circa 1870-1949 (Box 104, Folder 8)
  - Reproductions from photograph album of Rachel Anna and George Arthur Stuart, miscellaneous materials, circa 1850-1880 (Box 104, Folder 9)
  - Reproductions from photograph album of Rachel Anna and George Arthur Stuart, copy prints, circa 1850-1880 (Box 104, Folder 10)
  - George Arthur Stuart photographs, miscellaneous materials, circa 1870-1911 (Box 104, Folder 11)
  - George Arthur Stuart photographs, circa 1870-1911 (Box 104, Folder 12)
    - Photo 1 (Box 104, Folder 12, Item 1)
    - Photo 2 (Box 104, Folder 12, Item 2)
    - Photo 3 (Box 104, Folder 12, Item 3)
    - Photo 4 (Box 104, Folder 12, Item 4)
    - Photo 5 (Box 104, Folder 12, Item 5)
    - Photo 6 (Box 104, Folder 12, Item 6)
    - Photo 7 (Box 104, Folder 12, Item 7)
    - Photo 8 (Box 104, Folder 12, Item 8)
    - Photo 9 (Box 104, Folder 12, Item 9)
    - Photo 10 (Box 104, Folder 12, Item 10)
    - Photo 11 (Box 104, Folder 12, Item 11)
    - Photo 12 (Box 104, Folder 12, Item 12)
    - Photo 13 (Box 104, Folder 12, Item 13)
    - Photo 14 (Box 104, Folder 12, Item 14)
    - Photo 15 (Box 104, Folder 12, Item 15)
    - Photo 16 (Box 104, Folder 12, Item 16)
    - Photo 17 (Box 104, Folder 12, Item 17)
    - Photo 18 (Box 104, Folder 12, Item 18)
    - Photo 19 (Box 104, Folder 12, Item 19)
    - Photo 20 (Box 104, Folder 12, Item 20)
  - George Arthur Stuart photographs, copy prints (unique), circa 1870-1911 (Box 104, Folder 13)
    - Photo 1 (Box 104, Folder 13, Item 1)
    - Photo 2 (Box 104, Folder 13, Item 2)
    - Photo 3 (Box 104, Folder 13, Item 3)
  - George Arthur Stuart photographs, duplicates, circa 1870-1911 (Box 104, Folder 14)
  - George Arthur Stuart photographs, duplicates, circa 1870-1911 (Box 104, Folder 15)
  - Methodist Hospital, Nanking and Robert C. Beebe, photographs, circa 1886 (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - Photo 1 (Box 105, Folder 1, Item 1)
    - Photo 2 (Box 105, Folder 1, Item 2)
  - Wuhu General Hospital photographs, 1887-1897 (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - Photo 1 (Box 105, Folder 2, Item 1)
    - Photo 2 (Box 105, Folder 2, Item 2)
    - Photo 3 (Box 105, Folder 2, Item 3)
    - Photo 4 (Box 105, Folder 2, Item 4)
    - Photo 5 (Box 105, Folder 2, Item 5)
    - Photo 6 (Box 105, Folder 2, Item 6)
    - Photo 7 (Box 105, Folder 2, Item 7)
    - Photo 8 (Box 105, Folder 2, Item 8)
    - Photo 9 (Box 105, Folder 2, Item 9)
    - Photo 10 (Box 105, Folder 2, Item 10)
    - Photo 11 (Box 105, Folder 2, Item 11)
    - Photo 12 (Box 105, Folder 2, Item 12)
  - Wuhu General Hospital photographs, copy prints, 1887-1897 (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - Photo 1 (Box 105, Folder 3, Item 1)
    - Photo 2 (Box 105, Folder 3, Item 2)
    - Photo 3 (Box 105, Folder 3, Item 3)
    - Photo 4 (Box 105, Folder 3, Item 4)
    - Photo 5 (Box 105, Folder 3, Item 5)
    - Photo 6 (Box 105, Folder 3, Item 6)
    - Photo 7 (Box 105, Folder 3, Item 7)
    - Photo 8 (Box 105, Folder 3, Item 8)
    - Photo 9 (Box 105, Folder 3, Item 9)
    - Photo 10 (Box 105, Folder 3, Item 10)
    - Photo 11 (Box 105, Folder 3, Item 11)
    - Photo 12 (Box 105, Folder 3, Item 12)
    - Photo 13 (Box 105, Folder 3, Item 13)
    - Photo 14 (Box 105, Folder 3, Item 14)
  - Wuhu General Hospital photographs, duplicates, 1887-1897 (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - George Arthur Stuart, Newton (Mass.), photograph album, 1893 (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - University of Nanking photographs, miscellaneous materials, circa 1897-1911 (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - University of Nanking photographs, circa 1897-1911 (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - Photo 1 (Box 105, Folder 7, Item 1)
    - Photo 2 (Box 105, Folder 7, Item 2)
    - Photo 3 (Box 105, Folder 7, Item 3)
    - Photo 4 (Box 105, Folder 7, Item 4)
    - Photo 5 (Box 105, Folder 7, Item 5)
    - Photo 6 (Box 105, Folder 7, Item 6)
    - Photo 7 (Box 105, Folder 7, Item 7)
    - Photo 8 (Box 105, Folder 7, Item 8)
    - Photo 9 (Box 105, Folder 7, Item 9)
    - Photo 10 (Box 105, Folder 7, Item 10)
  - University of Nanking, students and buildings, circa 1910 (Box 239, Folder 1)
    - Photo 1 (Box 239, Folder 1, Item 1)
    - Photo 2 (Box 239, Folder 1, Item 2)
    - Photo 3 (Box 239, Folder 1, Item 3)
    - Photo 4 (Box 239, Folder 1, Item 4)
    - Photo 5 (Box 239, Folder 1, Item 5)
    - Photo 6 (Box 239, Folder 1, Item 6)
    - Photo 7 (Box 239, Folder 1, Item 7)
    - Photo 8 (Box 239, Folder 1, Item 8)
    - Photo 9 (Box 239, Folder 1, Item 9)
    - Photo 10 (Box 239, Folder 1, Item 10)
    - Photo 11 (Box 239, Folder 1, Item 11)
    - Photo 12 (Box 239, Folder 1, Item 12)
    - Photo 13 (Box 239, Folder 1, Item 13)
    - Photo 14 (Box 239, Folder 1, Item 14)
    - Photo 15 (Box 239, Folder 1, Item 15)
    - Photo 16 (Box 239, Folder 1, Item 16)
    - Photo 17 (Box 239, Folder 1, Item 17)
    - Photo 18 (Box 239, Folder 1, Item 18)
    - Photo 19 (Box 239, Folder 1, Item 19)
    - Photo 20 (Box 239, Folder 1, Item 20)
    - Photo 21 (Box 239, Folder 1, Item 21)
    - Photo 22 (Box 239, Folder 1, Item 22)
  - Cannon on the walls of Nanking, 1911 (Box 239, Folder 2)
  - Central China Missionary Conferences photographs, circa 1908-1911 (Box 105, Folder 8)
    - Photo 1 (Box 105, Folder 8, Item 1)
    - Photo 2 (Box 105, Folder 8, Item 2)
    - Photo 3 (Box 105, Folder 8, Item 3)
    - Photo 4 (Box 105, Folder 8, Item 4)
    - Photo 5 (Box 105, Folder 8, Item 5)
    - Photo 6 (Box 105, Folder 8, Item 6)
    - Photo 7 (Box 105, Folder 8, Item 7)
    - Photo 8 (Box 105, Folder 8, Item 8)
    - Photo 9 (Box 105, Folder 8, Item 9)
  - Central China Missionary Conferences, photographs, duplicates, circa 1908-1911 (Box 105, Folder 9)
  - George Arthur Stuart tombstone, photograph, 1911 (Box 105, Folder 10)
  - Chinese friends of Dr. and Mrs. George Arthur Stuart, photographs, miscellaneous, circa 1886-1911 (Box 105, Folder 11)
  - Chinese friends of Dr. and Mrs. George Arthur Stuart, photographs, circa 1886-1911 (Box 105, Folder 12)
    - Photo 1 (Box 105, Folder 12, Item 1)
    - Photo 2 (Box 105, Folder 12, Item 2)
    - Photo 3 (Box 105, Folder 12, Item 3)
    - Photo 4 (Box 105, Folder 12, Item 4)
    - Photo 5 (Box 105, Folder 12, Item 5)
    - Photo 6 (Box 105, Folder 12, Item 6)
    - Photo 7 (Box 105, Folder 12, Item 7)
    - Photo 8 (Box 105, Folder 12, Item 8)
    - Photo 9 (Box 105, Folder 12, Item 9)
    - Photo 10 (Box 105, Folder 12, Item 10)
    - Photo 11 (Box 105, Folder 12, Item 11)
    - Photo 12 (Box 105, Folder 12, Item 12)
    - Photo 13 (Box 105, Folder 12, Item 13)
    - Photo 14 (Box 105, Folder 12, Item 14)
    - Photo 15 (Box 105, Folder 12, Item 15)
    - Photo 16 (Box 105, Folder 12, Item 16)
    - Photo 17 (Box 105, Folder 12, Item 17)
  - Chinese friends of Dr. and Mrs. George Arthur Stuart, photographs, duplicates, circa 1886-1911 (Box 105, Folder 13)
  - Chinese friends of Dr. and Mrs. George Arthur Stuart, photographs, circa 1886-1911 (Flat-box 238, Folder 1)
    - Photo 1 (Flat-box 238, Folder 1, Item 1)
    - Photo 2 (Flat-box 238, Folder 1, Item 2)
  - Alcy Orma Stuart photographs, circa 1899-1924 (Box 105, Folder 14)
    - Photo 1 (Box 105, Folder 14, Item 1)
    - Photo 2 (Box 105, Folder 14, Item 2)
    - Photo 3 (Box 105, Folder 14, Item 3)
  - Alcy Orma Stuart photographs, copy prints, 1899 (Box 105, Folder 15)
    - Photo 1 (Box 105, Folder 15, Item 1)
    - Photo 2 (Box 105, Folder 15, Item 2)
  - Anna May Stuart photographs, circa 1915-1920 (Box 105, Folder 16)
    - Photo 1 (Box 105, Folder 16, Item 1)
    - Photo 2 (Box 105, Folder 16, Item 2)
    - Photo 3 (Box 105, Folder 16, Item 3)
    - Photo 4 (Box 105, Folder 16, Item 4)
    - Photo 5 (Box 105, Folder 16, Item 5)
    - Photo 6 (Box 105, Folder 16, Item 6)
    - Photo 7 (Box 105, Folder 16, Item 7)
    - Photo 8 (Box 105, Folder 16, Item 8)
    - Photo 9 (Box 105, Folder 16, Item 9)
    - Photo 10 (Box 105, Folder 16, Item 10)
    - Photo 11 (Box 105, Folder 16, Item 11)
    - Photo 12 (Box 105, Folder 16, Item 12)
    - Photo 13 (Box 105, Folder 16, Item 13)
    - Photo 14 (Box 105, Folder 16, Item 14)
    - Photo 15 (Box 105, Folder 16, Item 15)
    - Photo 16 (Box 105, Folder 16, Item 16)
    - Photo 17 (Box 105, Folder 16, Item 17)
    - Photo 18 (Box 105, Folder 16, Item 18)
    - Photo 19 (Box 105, Folder 16, Item 19)
    - Photo 20 (Box 105, Folder 16, Item 20)
  - Anna May Stuart photographs, circa 1915-1920 (Box 105, Folder 17)
    - Photo 1 (Box 105, Folder 17, Item 1)
    - Photo 2 (Box 105, Folder 17, Item 2)
    - Photo 3 (Box 105, Folder 17, Item 3)
    - Photo 4 (Box 105, Folder 17, Item 4)
    - Photo 5 (Box 105, Folder 17, Item 5)
    - Photo 6 (Box 105, Folder 17, Item 6)
    - Photo 7 (Box 105, Folder 17, Item 7)
    - Photo 8 (Box 105, Folder 17, Item 8)
    - Photo 9 (Box 105, Folder 17, Item 9)
    - Photo 10 (Box 105, Folder 17, Item 10)
    - Photo 11 (Box 105, Folder 17, Item 11)
    - Photo 12 (Box 105, Folder 17, Item 12)
    - Photo 13 (Box 105, Folder 17, Item 13)
  - Anna May Stuart photographs, circa 1940-2004 (Box 105, Folder 18)
  - Anna May Stuart photographs, negatives (Box 105, Folder 19)
  - Charles Melvin Stuart photographs, circa 1905-1955 (Box 105, Folder 20)
    - Photo 1 (Box 105, Folder 20, Item 1)
    - Photo 2 (Box 105, Folder 20, Item 2)
    - Photo 3 (Box 105, Folder 20, Item 3)
    - Photo 4 (Box 105, Folder 20, Item 4)
    - Photo 5 (Box 105, Folder 20, Item 5)
    - Photo 6 (Box 105, Folder 20, Item 6)
    - Photo 7 (Box 105, Folder 20, Item 7)
    - Photo 8 (Box 105, Folder 20, Item 8)
    - Photo 9 (Box 105, Folder 20, Item 9)
    - Photo 10 (Box 105, Folder 20, Item 10)
  - Charles Melvin Stuart photographs, duplicates, circa 1905-1955 (Box 105, Folder 21)
  - George Golden Stuart photographs, circa 1895-1927 (Box 105, Folder 22)
    - Photo 1 (Box 105, Folder 22, Item 1)
    - Photo 2 (Box 105, Folder 22, Item 2)
    - Photo 3 (Box 105, Folder 22, Item 3)
    - Photo 4 (Box 105, Folder 22, Item 4)
    - Photo 5 (Box 105, Folder 22, Item 5)
    - Photo 6 (Box 105, Folder 22, Item 6)
  - George Golden Stuart photographs, copy prints, circa 1905-1927 (Box 105, Folder 23)
  - Vera Stuart photographs, circa 1900-1920 (Box 105, Folder 24)
    - Photo 1 (Box 105, Folder 24, Item 1)
    - Photo 2 (Box 105, Folder 24, Item 2)
    - Photo 3 (Box 105, Folder 24, Item 3)
    - Photo 4 (Box 105, Folder 24, Item 4)
  - Mildred Stuart Hummel, early photographs, miscellaneous materials, circa 1884-1915 (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Mildred Stuart Hummel, early photographs, circa 1884-1915 (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - Photo 1 (Box 106, Folder 2, Item 1)
    - Photo 2 (Box 106, Folder 2, Item 2)
    - Photo 3 (Box 106, Folder 2, Item 3)
    - Photo 4 (Box 106, Folder 2, Item 4)
    - Photo 5 (Box 106, Folder 2, Item 5)
    - Photo 6 (Box 106, Folder 2, Item 6)
    - Photo 7 (Box 106, Folder 2, Item 7)
    - Photo 8 (Box 106, Folder 2, Item 8)
    - Photo 9 (Box 106, Folder 2, Item 9)
    - Photo 10 (Box 106, Folder 2, Item 10)
    - Photo 11 (Box 106, Folder 2, Item 11)
    - Photo 12 (Box 106, Folder 2, Item 12)
    - Photo 13 (Box 106, Folder 2, Item 13)
    - Photo 14 (Box 106, Folder 2, Item 14)
    - Photo 15 (Box 106, Folder 2, Item 15)
    - Photo 16 (Box 106, Folder 2, Item 16)
    - Photo 17 (Box 106, Folder 2, Item 17)
    - Photo 18 (Box 106, Folder 2, Item 18)
    - Photo 19 (Box 106, Folder 2, Item 19)
    - Photo 20 (Box 106, Folder 2, Item 20)
    - Photo 21 (Box 106, Folder 2, Item 21)
  - Mildred Stuart Hummel, early photographs, circa 1884-1915 (Box 106, Folder 3)
    - Photo 1 (Box 106, Folder 3, Item 1)
    - Photo 2 (Box 106, Folder 3, Item 2)
    - Photo 3 (Box 106, Folder 3, Item 3)
    - Photo 4 (Box 106, Folder 3, Item 4)
    - Photo 5 (Box 106, Folder 3, Item 5)
    - Photo 6 (Box 106, Folder 3, Item 6)
    - Photo 7 (Box 106, Folder 3, Item 7)
    - Photo 8 (Box 106, Folder 3, Item 8)
    - Photo 9 (Box 106, Folder 3, Item 9)
    - Photo 10 (Box 106, Folder 3, Item 10)
    - Photo 11 (Box 106, Folder 3, Item 11)
    - Photo 12 (Box 106, Folder 3, Item 12)
    - Photo 13 (Box 106, Folder 3, Item 13)
    - Photo 14 (Box 106, Folder 3, Item 14)
    - Photo 15 (Box 106, Folder 3, Item 15)
    - Photo 16 (Box 106, Folder 3, Item 16)
    - Photo 17 (Box 106, Folder 3, Item 17)
    - Photo 18 (Box 106, Folder 3, Item 18)
    - Photo 19 (Box 106, Folder 3, Item 19)
    - Photo 20 (Box 106, Folder 3, Item 20)
    - Photo 21 (Box 106, Folder 3, Item 21)
    - Photo 22 (Box 106, Folder 3, Item 22)
    - Photo 23 (Box 106, Folder 3, Item 23)
    - Photo 24 (Box 106, Folder 3, Item 24)
    - Photo 25 (Box 106, Folder 3, Item 25)
    - Photo 26 (Box 106, Folder 3, Item 26)
    - Photo 27 (Box 106, Folder 3, Item 27)
    - Photo 28 (Box 106, Folder 3, Item 28)
    - Photo 29 (Box 106, Folder 3, Item 29)
    - Photo 30 (Box 106, Folder 3, Item 30)
  - Mildred Stuart Hummel, early photographs, circa 1884-1915 (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - Photo 1 (Box 106, Folder 4, Item 1)
    - Photo 2 (Box 106, Folder 4, Item 2)
    - Photo 3 (Box 106, Folder 4, Item 3)
    - Photo 4 (Box 106, Folder 4, Item 4)
    - Photo 5 (Box 106, Folder 4, Item 5)
    - Photo 6 (Box 106, Folder 4, Item 6)
    - Photo 7 (Box 106, Folder 4, Item 7)
    - Photo 8 (Box 106, Folder 4, Item 8)
    - Photo 9 (Box 106, Folder 4, Item 9)
    - Photo 10 (Box 106, Folder 4, Item 10)
    - Photo 11 (Box 106, Folder 4, Item 11)
    - Photo 12 (Box 106, Folder 4, Item 12)
    - Photo 13 (Box 106, Folder 4, Item 13)
    - Photo 14 (Box 106, Folder 4, Item 14)
    - Photo 15 (Box 106, Folder 4, Item 15)
    - Photo 16 (Box 106, Folder 4, Item 16)
    - Photo 17 (Box 106, Folder 4, Item 17)
    - Photo 18 (Box 106, Folder 4, Item 18)
    - Photo 19 (Box 106, Folder 4, Item 19)
    - Photo 20 (Box 106, Folder 4, Item 20)
    - Photo 21 (Box 106, Folder 4, Item 21)
    - Photo 22 (Box 106, Folder 4, Item 22)
    - Photo 23 (Box 106, Folder 4, Item 23)
    - Photo 24 (Box 106, Folder 4, Item 24)
    - Photo 25 (Box 106, Folder 4, Item 25)
    - Photo 26 (Box 106, Folder 4, Item 26)
  - Mildred Stuart Hummel, early photographs, circa 1884-1915 (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - Photo 1 (Box 106, Folder 5, Item 1)
    - Photo 2 (Box 106, Folder 5, Item 2)
    - Photo 3 (Box 106, Folder 5, Item 3)
    - Photo 4 (Box 106, Folder 5, Item 4)
    - Photo 5 (Box 106, Folder 5, Item 5)
    - Photo 6 (Box 106, Folder 5, Item 6)
    - Photo 7 (Box 106, Folder 5, Item 7)
    - Photo 8 (Box 106, Folder 5, Item 8)